hyperxlocal.com 2014-05-25

# Privacy Policy | HyperX Media: Utah Advertising

**Privacy Policy**

HyperX Media Privacy Policy Effective Date: January 27, 2006 HyperX Media (HXL) believes that privacy and security are of major concern to online users. Therefore, we have adopted the policy below, which discloses the privacy and security practices for our site. This privacy policy is applicable to www.HyperXLocal.com and other sites on the World Wide Web owned and operated by HyperX Media. The policy is designed to inform you of:

  * What information we might gather from you
  * What we will do with that information
  * What benefits you may receive by our use of that information
  * How you can control the information you choose to submit on our site
  * What protections we provide for the online privacy of children
  * How you can correct and update your Member information, opt-out of communications, or delete your information from the database

Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, our site has agreed to disclose its information practices. If you have questions regarding this policy, please contact our policy director at:support@HyperXLocal.com ****

**Our Privacy Vow**

We at HyperX Media (HXL) believe that strong electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service and as a commercial, educational, and entertainment medium. However, we do need to understand user behavior in order to serve you better. To achieve this goal, we need to understand what differentiates you from other unique users of the site. We may collect information about our Members in two ways: at registration and with cookies. ****

**Information We May Ask You to Provide at Registration**

HXL gathers information about our Members that allows us to offer compelling services and easily accessible online content in a manner that provides personal privacy protection as well. When you register, we request and collect personal information including your name, phone number and e-mail address in order for you to participate in various online services and other activities. This information also helps us provide content that is relevant to you. It is up to you to decide whether you wish to participate in these activities and provide the required information. We do NOT collect Social Security numbers. Credit card information, such as card numbers and expiration dates, are collected only when purchases are made and are used for purchase transactions only. This information is used solely in the event of a commercial transaction. HXL may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its visitors. Please be aware that any information that you disclose in these areas becomes public information, so you should exercise caution in disclosing personal information. HXL will not disclose your personal information and passwords to other visitors in any of the public forums. We may also request information about your likes, dislikes, purchasing habits, and online activities. This information helps HXL deliver content and activities that are customized and relevant to your preferences. This information may be made available to our corporate sponsors in varying degrees of complexity, but only if you have given your permission for this to occur. Along with all of our Members, you will receive periodic electronic-mail messages covering such topics as the confirmation of initial registration, any subsequent email newsletters with information about integrated marketing strategies. You may at any time cancel your Membership with HXL. Information We May Implicitly Collect ****

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small bits of information that a Web site transfers to your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web surfing easier by saving your registration, passwords, and preferences: they allow you to be recognized when you return to the site. The use of cookies is an industry-wide practice and you’ll find them at most major Web sites. By “looking” for a cookie, our server can determine whether you have already registered as a Member of our site. As a result, if you are a Member, you may see a customized front page and will not need to re-register each time you log on. Cookies also help us to serve you better by improving the site. They allow HXL to track your interests and add content that is more relevant to you. Most Web browsers are usually set to initially accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, the site may not function properly if you do not accept cookies. Acceptance of a HyperXLocal.com Membership obligates you to accept our cookies. ****

**Collecting IP Addresses**

HXL collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information. An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you register on the HXL Site, our servers log the Members’ IP addresses. We, in turn, use this information to track navigation through the site and to improve the performance of the HXL online experience. In addition, HyperXLocal.com uses third party tracking services to analyze traffic to this web site. The tracking does not create individual profiles for visitors, and does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. ****

**Collecting Interests**

In general, HXL does not collect Site Member information simply based on your interactions with our site. However, we may make note of your interest or disinterest in a particular subject via a simple numeric value added to your Member profile. This value indicates your relative interest or disinterest in a particular subject when you complete specific events or activities that are meaningful to us in understanding how to provide you with better customer support. ****

**Sharing of Information**

HXL will never will fully disclose individually identifiable information about you to any third party without first receiving your permission. We will use your individually identifiable information only within our site to provide a personalized experience to you. It may also be shared with HXL’s partners that provide some of the personalized content on our site, but only if you have given your permission for this to occur. Our privacy guarantee to you remains unchanged.

CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS: Your Privacy Rights

Starting January 1, 2005, companies that collect personally identifiable information from California residents and disclose such information to third parties (including affiliated entities) for marketing purposes must, in response to a request by a consumer, either provide a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided – or provide a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with third parties. You may request that your information not be shared by sending a written letter including your full name and email address to: HyperX Media 102 West 12200 South | Draper, UT 84020. Please contact us with any questions or concerns about your privacy rights. ****

**Opt-Out Features**

HXL believes the users of the site should control the communications directed to them. Every time we collect name and address information about you: You can tell us if you don’t wish to receive communications from HyperXLocal.com such as e-mail newsletters announcing new features; you can tell us if you don’t want to receive communications from third-party companies that offer a product or service we think would be of value to you. ****

**Conclusion**

HyperX Media fully respects your privacy and security concerns. We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the HXL Site following the posting of changes to these Terms of Service will mean that you accept those changes. If you have any questions or concerns about the HyperX Media Privacy Policy, please email support@HyperXLocal.com, or call 801-566-0670.  
Updated 1/27/2006

Simply fill out the form below to get a customized quote in no time.

Do you have a popular website with a solid local audience? We'll pay you to advertise on it. Just fill out the form below and we'll be in touch.
